Hello everyone, My name is gracing
wolves
expansion RPG System
today well expanzer PG System Slow
leshaping The System your Build Into The
actureal
centroduce acuracy of Attack Open
carctorscript
Create New variable Cold acuresy of Type
float
everywhere Fold Zero Point sometry Five
ahmeds you have Script
Number between Zero and One
C and tminskoy rector Mist itza so
Target
good
on the street rain through Open karacter renz a
Dodge Chance Same float War Rainbow
bitvisiruya 2 One mining Hunter sandech
vantu interview schinstvu converter
Normal Attack intu High demijinga so
maketowerible Creed Chance Witch resenti
probobility of diring the Critical
Attack and Creed demage multiplikater
HIV representze inkrisov The damage if
you Hit the Critical Attack
from Aura so and with critical hit New Yes The
totalo mounta in demo 4 koulus solec
gedza a  Mounts dimage outerctor can do
intelsappy Red War Rainbow manipolate
sovic apply All canzov modifications to
This Wella
And The New randa Velo and comparet
again Star Critical Chance
and franda veylo from love and Twin This
Strike from Critical
and our damage not studio multiplyvat bays
damage multiplikater
Good vydelevera Critical Strike
This Apple Pajero support of people on
Patriot and bemerson YouTube and fivanto
jetzer link again equal from description
Engine baton avel Right Now On YouTube
so author wichek for Critical Strike
modify themage Buy The armor of the
carector
this
owls introdist minimum Flor for our
damage pitches One
goods price is minimal Mount of damage our
enemicken take from One votvativ there
not from physicists world of physicists demoji with
dekrist boyarmor Pavel Magic damage cries
by Resistance
introduction Inside The Attack Cold
demith Type wist To members physical and
magical brought out
attack or character string to do then
Side carector introduce damage Type N
Resistance for Rainbow
Good insidea and in The carector Attack
from physics Type brought out US armor any Fat
is magic Type brought out use Resistance to
decrease incoming damage
and setaworker attack to be magical As You
cancy names
dazonstop Power magical attackset to
bezical his hai armarvielstop Most of
the incamage
Below and Fur interestinginy in this team
vivantus parfjurza petren in the
description Special thank you to echmey
the sould has do and revilong with Best
reguards seinzine ext Episode